{
    "name": "Kanji N3", 
    "vocab": [
        {
            "answer": "deliberation, consultation, debate, consideration", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"議\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "議", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"deliberation, consultation, debate, consideration\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "people, nation, subjects", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"民\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "民", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"people, nation, subjects\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ミン タ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"民\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "take along, lead, join, connect, party, gang, clique", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"連\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "連", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"take along, lead, join, connect, party, gang, clique\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レン -ヅ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"連\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つら.なる つら.ねる つ.れる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"連\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "vis-a-vis, opposite, even, equal, versus, anti-, compare", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"対\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "対", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"vis-a-vis, opposite, even, equal, versus, anti-, compare\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タイ ツイ ムカ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"対\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あいて こた.える そろ.い つれあ.い なら.ぶ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"対\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "section, bureau, dept, class, copy, part, portion, counter for copies of a newspaper or magazine", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"部\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "部", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"section, bureau, dept, class, copy, part, portion, counter for copies of a newspaper or magazine\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ブ -", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"部\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fit, suit, join, 0.1", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"合\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "合", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fit, suit, join, 0.1\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゴウ ガッ カッ -ア.ワセ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"合\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あ.う -あ.う あ.い あい- -あ.い -あい あ.わす あ.わせる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"合\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "market, city, town", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"市\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "市", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"market, city, town\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シ イ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"市\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "inside, within, between, among, house, home", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"内\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "内", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"inside, within, between, among, house, home\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ナイ ダイ ウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"内\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "inter-, mutual, together, each other, minister of state, councillor, aspect, phase, physiognomy", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"相\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "相", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"inter-, mutual, together, each other, minister of state, councillor, aspect, phase, physiognomy\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソウ ショウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"相\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"相\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "determine, fix, establish, decide", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"定\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "定", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"determine, fix, establish, decide\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テイ ジョウ サダ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"定\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さだ.める さだ.まる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"定\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "-times, round, game, revolve, counter for occurrences", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"回\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "回", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"-times, round, game, revolve, counter for occurrences\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カイ エ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"回\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まわ.る -まわ.る -まわ.り まわ.す -まわ.す まわ.し- -まわ.し もとお.る か.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"回\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "elect, select, choose, prefer", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"選\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "選", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"elect, select, choose, prefer\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"選\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "えら.ぶ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"選\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rice, USA, metre", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"米\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "米", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rice, USA, metre\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ベイ マイ メエトル ヨ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"米\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こめ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"米\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "reality, truth", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"実\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "実", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"reality, truth\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジツ シツ ミチ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"実\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "み みの.る まこと まことに みの", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"実\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "connection, barrier, gateway, involve, concerning", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"関\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "関", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"connection, barrier, gateway, involve, concerning\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"関\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せき -ぜき かか.わる からくり かんぬき", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"関\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "decide, fix, agree upon, appoint", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"決\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "決", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"decide, fix, agree upon, appoint\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"決\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "き.める -ぎ.め き.まる さ.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"決\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "whole, entire, all, complete, fulfill", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"全\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "全", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"whole, entire, all, complete, fulfill\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゼン スベ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"全\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まった.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"全\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "surface, table, chart, diagram", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"表\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "表", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"surface, table, chart, diagram\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"表\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おもて -おもて あらわ.す あらわ.れる あら.わす", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"表\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "war, battle, match", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"戦\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "戦", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"war, battle, match\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セン ワナナ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"戦\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いくさ たたか.う おのの.く そよぐ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"戦\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sutra, longitude, pass thru, expire, warp", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"経\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "経", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sutra, longitude, pass thru, expire, warp\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケイ キョウ ノ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"経\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "へ.る た.つ たていと はか.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"経\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "utmost, most, extreme", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"最\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "最", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"utmost, most, extreme\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サイ シュ ツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"最\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もっと.も", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"最\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "present, existing, actual", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"現\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "現", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"present, existing, actual\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゲン アラワ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"現\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あらわ.れる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"現\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tune, tone, meter, key (music), writing style, prepare, exorcise, investigate", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"調\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "調", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tune, tone, meter, key (music), writing style, prepare, exorcise, investigate\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "チョウ トトノ.エ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"調\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しら.べる しら.べ ととの.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"調\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "change, take the form of, influence, enchant, delude, -ization", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"化\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "化", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"change, take the form of, influence, enchant, delude, -ization\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カ ケ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"化\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ば.ける ば.かす ふ.ける け.する", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"化\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hit, right, appropriate, himself", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"当\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "当", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hit, right, appropriate, himself\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トウ マサ.ニベ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"当\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あ.たる あ.たり あ.てる あ.て まさ.に", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"当\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "promise, approximately, shrink", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"約\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "約", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"promise, approximately, shrink\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヤク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"約\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "neck", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"首\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "首", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"neck\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シュ ク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"首\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "method, law, rule, principle, model, system", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"法\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "法", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"method, law, rule, principle, model, system\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ホウ ハッ ホッ フラン ノ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"法\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sex, gender, nature", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"性\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "性", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sex, gender, nature\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セイ ショウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"性\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さが", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"性\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "need, main point, essence, pivot, key to", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"要\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "要", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"need, main point, essence, pivot, key to\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヨウ イ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"要\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "system, law, rule", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"制\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "制", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"system, law, rule\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"制\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "reign, be at peace, calm down, subdue, quell, govt, cure, heal, rule, conserve", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"治\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "治", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"reign, be at peace, calm down, subdue, quell, govt, cure, heal, rule, conserve\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジ チ ナオ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"治\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おさ.める おさ.まる なお.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"治\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "task, duties", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"務\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "務", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"task, duties\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ム ツト.メ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"務\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "turn into, become, get, grow, elapse, reach", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"成\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "成", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"turn into, become, get, grow, elapse, reach\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セイ ジョウ -ナ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"成\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "な.る な.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"成\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "period, time, date, term", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"期\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "期", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"period, time, date, term\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キ ゴ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"期\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "take, fetch, take up", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"取\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "取", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"take, fetch, take up\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シュ -ド.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"取\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "と.る と.り と.り- とり", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"取\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "metropolis, capital", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"都\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "都", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"metropolis, capital\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ト ツ ミヤ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"都\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "harmony, Japanese style, peace, soften, Japan", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"和\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "和", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"harmony, Japanese style, peace, soften, Japan\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ワ オ カ ナゴ.ヤ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"和\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やわ.らぐ やわ.らげる なご.む", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"和\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mechanism, opportunity, occasion, machine, airplane", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"機\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "機", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mechanism, opportunity, occasion, machine, airplane\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"機\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はた", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"機\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "even, flat, peace", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"平\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "平", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"even, flat, peace\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヘイ ビョウ ヒョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"平\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たい.ら -だいら ひら ひら", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"平\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "add, addition, increase, join, include, Canada", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"加\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "加", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"add, addition, increase, join, include, Canada\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"加\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くわ.える くわ.わる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"加\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "accept, undergo, answer (phone), take, get, catch, receive", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"受\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "受", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"accept, undergo, answer (phone), take, get, catch, receive\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジュ ウ.カ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"受\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "う.ける -う.け", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"受\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "continue, series, sequel", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"続\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "続", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"continue, series, sequel\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゾク ショク コウ キョウ ツグ.ナ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"続\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つづ.く つづ.ける", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"続\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "advance, proceed, progress, promote", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"進\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "進", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"advance, proceed, progress, promote\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シン スス.メ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"進\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すす.む", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"進\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "number, strength, fate, law, figures", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"数\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "数", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"number, strength, fate, law, figures\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "スウ ス サク ソク シュ ワズラワ.シ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"数\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かず かぞ.える しばしば せ.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"数\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "scribe, account, narrative", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"記\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "記", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"scribe, account, narrative\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キ シル.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"記\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "first time, beginning", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"初\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "初", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"first time, beginning\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショ -ゾ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"初\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はじ.め はじ.めて はつ はつ- うい- -そ.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"初\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "finger, point to, indicate, put into, play (chess), measure (ruler)", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"指\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "指", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"finger, point to, indicate, put into, play (chess), measure (ruler)\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シ -サ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"指\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆび さ.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"指\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "authority, power, rights", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"権\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "権", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"authority, power, rights\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケン ゴン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"権\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おもり かり はか.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"権\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "branch, support, sustain", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"支\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "支", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"branch, support, sustain\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しんよう じゅうまた", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"支\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "products, bear, give birth, yield, childbirth, native, property", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"産\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "産", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"products, bear, give birth, yield, childbirth, native, property\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サン ム.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"産\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "う.む う.まれる うぶ-", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"産\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "spot, point, mark, speck, decimal point", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"点\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "点", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"spot, point, mark, speck, decimal point\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"点\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つ.ける つ.く た.てる さ.す とぼ.す とも.す ぼち", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"点\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "report, news, reward, retribution", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"報\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "報", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"report, news, reward, retribution\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ホウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"報\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むく.いる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"報\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "finish, come to an end, excusable, need not", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"済\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "済", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"finish, come to an end, excusable, need not\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サイ セイ ワタ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"済\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "す.む -ず.み -ずみ す.まない す.ます -す.ます すく.う な.す わたし", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"済\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lively, resuscitation, being helped, living", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"活\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "活", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lively, resuscitation, being helped, living\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"活\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "い.きる い.かす い.ける", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"活\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "meadow, original, primitive, field, plain, prairie, tundra, wilderness", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"原\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "原", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"meadow, original, primitive, field, plain, prairie, tundra, wilderness\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゲン ハ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"原\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "together, both, neither, all, and, alike, with", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"共\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "共", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"together, both, neither, all, and, alike, with\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"共\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とも とも.に -ども", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"共\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gain, get, find, earn, acquire, can, may, able to, profit, advantage, benefit", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"得\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "得", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gain, get, find, earn, acquire, can, may, able to, profit, advantage, benefit\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トク ウ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"得\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "え.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"得\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "unravel, notes, key, explanation, understanding, untie, undo, solve, answer, cancel, absolve, explain, minute", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"解\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "解", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"unravel, notes, key, explanation, understanding, untie, undo, solve, answer, cancel, absolve, explain, minute\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カイ ゲ サト.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"解\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "と.く と.かす と.ける ほど.く ほど.ける わか.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"解\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mingle, mixing, association, coming & going", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"交\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "交", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mingle, mixing, association, coming & going\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ コモゴ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"交\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まじ.わる まじ.える ま.じる まじ.る ま.ざる ま.ぜる -か.う か.わす かわ.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"交\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "assets, resources, capital, funds, data, be conducive to, contribute to", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"資\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "資", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"assets, resources, capital, funds, data, be conducive to, contribute to\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "beforehand, previous, myself, I", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"予\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "予", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"beforehand, previous, myself, I\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヨ シャ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"予\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あらかじ.め", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"予\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "yonder, facing, beyond, confront, defy, tend toward, approach", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"向\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "向", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"yonder, facing, beyond, confront, defy, tend toward, approach\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ ムカ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"向\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "む.く む.い -む.き む.ける -む.け む.かう む.かい む.こう む.こう- むこ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"向\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "occasion, side, edge, verge, dangerous, adventurous, indecent, time, when", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"際\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "際", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"occasion, side, edge, verge, dangerous, adventurous, indecent, time, when\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サイ -ギ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"際\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きわ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"際\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "victory, win, prevail, excel", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"勝\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "勝", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"victory, win, prevail, excel\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショウ カ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"勝\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "か.つ -が.ち まさ.る すぐ.れる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"勝\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mask, face, features, surface", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"面\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "面", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mask, face, features, surface\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "メン ベン ツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"面\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おも おもて", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"面\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "revelation, tell, inform, announce", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"告\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "告", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"revelation, tell, inform, announce\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コク ツ.ゲ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"告\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "anti-", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"反\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "反", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"anti-\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハン ホン タン ホ -カエ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"反\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そ.る そ.らす かえ.す かえ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"反\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "judgement, signature, stamp, seal", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"判\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "判", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"judgement, signature, stamp, seal\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハン バン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"判\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わか.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"判\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "acknowledge, witness, discern, recognize, appreciate, believe", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"認\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "認", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"acknowledge, witness, discern, recognize, appreciate, believe\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ニン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"認\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みと.める したた.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"認\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "nonplussed, three, going, coming, visiting, visit, be defeated, die, be madly in love", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"参\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "参", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"nonplussed, three, going, coming, visiting, visit, be defeated, die, be madly in love\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サン シン ミ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"参\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まい.る まい- まじわる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"参\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "profit, advantage, benefit", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"利\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "利", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"profit, advantage, benefit\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "リ キ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"利\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "association, braid, plait, construct, assemble, unite, cooperate, grapple", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"組\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "組", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"association, braid, plait, construct, assemble, unite, cooperate, grapple\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"組\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "く.む くみ -ぐみ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"組\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "faith, truth, fidelity, trust", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"信\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "信", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"faith, truth, fidelity, trust\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"信\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "exist, outskirts, suburbs, located in", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"在\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "在", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"exist, outskirts, suburbs, located in\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ザイ ア.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"在\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "affair, case, matter, item", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"件\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "件", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"affair, case, matter, item\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"件\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くだん", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"件\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "side, lean, oppose, regret", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"側\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "側", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"side, lean, oppose, regret\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"側\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かわ がわ そば", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"側\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "responsibility, duty, term, entrust to, appoint", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"任\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "任", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"responsibility, duty, term, entrust to, appoint\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ニン マカ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"任\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まか.せる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"任\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pull, tug, jerk, admit, install, quote, refer to", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"引\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "引", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pull, tug, jerk, admit, install, quote, refer to\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "イン ヒ.ケ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"引\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひ.く ひ.き ひ.き- -び.き", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"引\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "request, want, wish for, require, demand", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"求\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "求", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"request, want, wish for, require, demand\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キュウ グ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"求\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もと.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"求\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "place", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"所\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "所", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"place\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショ ト", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"所\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ところ -ところ どころ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"所\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "next, order, sequence", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"次\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "次", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"next, order, sequence\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジ シ ツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"次\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つ.ぐ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"次\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "yesterday, previous", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"昨\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "昨", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"yesterday, previous\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"昨\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "argument, discourse", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"論\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "論", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"argument, discourse\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ロン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"論\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bureaucrat, the government", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"官\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "官", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bureaucrat, the government\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"官\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "increase, add, augment, gain, promote", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"増\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "増", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"increase, add, augment, gain, promote\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゾウ フ.ヤ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"増\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ま.す ま.し ふ.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"増\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "person in charge, connection, duty, concern oneself", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"係\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "係", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"person in charge, connection, duty, concern oneself\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"係\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かか.る かかり -がかり かか.わる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"係\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "emotion, feeling, sensation", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"感\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "感", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"emotion, feeling, sensation\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"感\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "feelings, emotion, passion, sympathy, circumstances, facts", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"情\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "情", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"feelings, emotion, passion, sympathy, circumstances, facts\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジョウ セイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"情\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なさ.け", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"情\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "throw, discard, abandon, launch into, join, invest in, hurl, give up, sell at a loss", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"投\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "投", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"throw, discard, abandon, launch into, join, invest in, hurl, give up, sell at a loss\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"投\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "な.げる -な.げ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"投\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "show, indicate, point out, express, display", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"示\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "示", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"show, indicate, point out, express, display\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジ シ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"示\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しめ.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"示\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "unusual, change, strange", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"変\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "変", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"unusual, change, strange\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヘン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"変\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "か.わる か.わり か.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"変\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "strike, hit, knock, pound, dozen", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"打\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "打", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"strike, hit, knock, pound, dozen\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ダ ダアス ブ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"打\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "う.つ う.ち-", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"打\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "straightaway, honesty, frankness, fix, repair", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"直\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "直", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"straightaway, honesty, frankness, fix, repair\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "チョク ジキ ジカ ス.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"直\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ただ.ちに なお.す -なお.す なお.る なお.き", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"直\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "both, old Japanese coin, counter for vehicles, two", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"両\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "両", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"both, old Japanese coin, counter for vehicles, two\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "リョウ フタ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"両\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "てる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"両\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "style, ceremony, rite, function, method, system, form, expression", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"式\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "式", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"style, ceremony, rite, function, method, system, form, expression\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"式\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "assurance, firm, tight, hard, solid, confirm, clear, evident", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"確\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "確", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"assurance, firm, tight, hard, solid, confirm, clear, evident\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カク コウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"確\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たし.か たし.かめる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"確\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fruit, reward, carry out, achieve, complete, end, finish, succeed", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"果\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "果", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fruit, reward, carry out, achieve, complete, end, finish, succeed\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カ ハ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"果\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "は.たす はた.す -は.たす は.てる -は.てる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"果\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "contain, form, looks", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"容\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "容", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"contain, form, looks\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヨウ イ.レ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"容\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "invariably, certain, inevitable", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"必\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "必", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"invariably, certain, inevitable\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"必\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かなら.ず", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"必\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "performance, act, play, render, stage", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"演\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "演", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"performance, act, play, render, stage\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "エン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"演\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "year-end, age, occasion, opportunity", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"歳\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "歳", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"year-end, age, occasion, opportunity\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サイ セイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"歳\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "とし とせ よわい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"歳\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "contend, dispute, argue", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"争\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "争", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"contend, dispute, argue\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"争\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あらそ.う いか.でか", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"争\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "discuss, talk", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"談\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "談", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"discuss, talk\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ダン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"談\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ability, talent, skill, capacity", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"能\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "能", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ability, talent, skill, capacity\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ノウ ヨ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"能\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rank, grade, throne, crown, about, some", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"位\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "位", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rank, grade, throne, crown, about, some\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "イ グラ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"位\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くらい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"位\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "placement, put, set, deposit, leave behind, keep, employ, pawn", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"置\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "置", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"placement, put, set, deposit, leave behind, keep, employ, pawn\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "チ -オ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"置\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"置\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "current, a sink, flow, forfeit", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"流\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "流", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"current, a sink, flow, forfeit\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "リュウ ル -ナガ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"流\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "なが.れる なが.れ なが.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"流\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "status, rank, capacity, character, case (law, grammar)", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"格\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "格", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"status, rank, capacity, character, case (law, grammar)\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カク コウ キャク ゴ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"格\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "doubt, distrust, be suspicious, question", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"疑\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "疑", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"doubt, distrust, be suspicious, question\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ギ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"疑\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うたが.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"疑\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "overdo, exceed, go beyond, error", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"過\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "過", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"overdo, exceed, go beyond, error\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"過\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "す.ぎる -す.ぎる -す.ぎ す.ごす あやま.つ あやま.ち", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"過\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bureau, board, office, affair, conclusion, court lady, lady-in-waiting, her apartment", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"局\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "局", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bureau, board, office, affair, conclusion, court lady, lady-in-waiting, her apartment\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キョク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"局\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つぼね", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"局\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "set free, release, fire, shoot, emit, banish, liberate", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"放\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "放", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"set free, release, fire, shoot, emit, banish, liberate\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ホウ ホウ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"放\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はな.す -っぱな.し はな.つ はな.れる こ.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"放\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "usual, ordinary, normal, regular", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"常\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "常", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"usual, ordinary, normal, regular\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"常\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つね とこ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"常\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "status quo, conditions, circumstances, form, appearance", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"状\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "状", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"status quo, conditions, circumstances, form, appearance\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"状\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ball, sphere", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"球\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "球", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ball, sphere\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キュウ タ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"球\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "post, employment, work", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"職\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "職", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"post, employment, work\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショク ソ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"職\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bestow, participate in, give, award, impart, provide, cause, gift, godsend", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"与\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "与", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bestow, participate in, give, award, impart, provide, cause, gift, godsend\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヨ トモ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"与\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あた.える あずか.る くみ.する", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"与\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "submit, offer, present, serve (meal), accompany", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"供\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "供", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"submit, offer, present, serve (meal), accompany\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キョウ ク クウ グ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"供\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そな.える とも -ども", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"供\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "duty, war, campaign, drafted labor, office, service, role", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"役\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "役", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"duty, war, campaign, drafted labor, office, service, role\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヤク エ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"役\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "posture, build, pretend", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"構\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "構", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"posture, build, pretend\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ カマ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"構\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かま.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"構\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "proportion, comparatively, divide, cut, separate, split", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"割\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "割", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"proportion, comparatively, divide, cut, separate, split\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"割\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わ.る わり わ.り わ.れる さ.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"割\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "expense, cost, spend, consume, waste", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"費\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "費", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"expense, cost, spend, consume, waste\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"費\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つい.やす つい.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"費\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "adhere, attach, refer to, append", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"付\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "付", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"adhere, attach, refer to, append\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フ -ヅ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"付\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つ.ける -つ.ける -づ.ける つ.け つ.け- -つ.け -づ.け -づけ つ.く -づ.く つ.き -つ.き -つ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"付\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "wherefore, a reason", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"由\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "由", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"wherefore, a reason\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ユ ユウ ユイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"由\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よし よ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"由\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rumor, opinion, theory", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"説\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "説", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rumor, opinion, theory\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セツ ゼイ ト.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"説\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "difficult, impossible, trouble, accident, defect", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"難\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "難", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"difficult, impossible, trouble, accident, defect\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ナン -ニク.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"難\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かた.い -がた.い むずか.しい むづか.しい むつか.しい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"難\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tenderness, excel, surpass, actor, superiority, gentleness", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"優\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "優", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tenderness, excel, surpass, actor, superiority, gentleness\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ユウ ウ マサ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"優\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やさ.しい すぐ.れる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"優\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "husband, man", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"夫\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "夫", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"husband, man\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フ フウ ブ ソ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"夫\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おっと", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"夫\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "income, obtain, reap, pay, supply, store", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"収\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "収", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"income, obtain, reap, pay, supply, store\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シュウ オサ.マ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"収\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おさ.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"収\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "severance, decline, refuse, apologize, warn, dismiss, prohibit, decision, judgement, cutting", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"断\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "断", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"severance, decline, refuse, apologize, warn, dismiss, prohibit, decision, judgement, cutting\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ダン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"断\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "た.つ ことわ.る さだ.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"断\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "stone", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"石\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "石", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"stone\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セキ シャク コク イ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"石\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "difference, differ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"違\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "違", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"difference, differ\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "イ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"違\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ちが.う ちが.い ちが.える -ちが.える たが.う たが.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"違\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "extinguish, blow out, turn off, neutralize, cancel", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"消\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "消", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"extinguish, blow out, turn off, neutralize, cancel\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"消\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "き.える け.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"消\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "gods, mind, soul", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"神\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "神", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"gods, mind, soul\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シン ジン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"神\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かみ かん- こう", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"神\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "turn, number in a series", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"番\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "番", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"turn, number in a series\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "バン ツガ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"番\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "standard, measure", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"規\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "規", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"standard, measure\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "art, technique, skill, means, trick, resources, magic", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"術\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "術", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"art, technique, skill, means, trick, resources, magic\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジュツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"術\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すべ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"術\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "equip, provision, preparation", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"備\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "備", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"equip, provision, preparation\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ビ ツブサ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"備\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そな.える そな.わる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"備\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "home, house, residence, our house, my husband", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"宅\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "宅", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"home, house, residence, our house, my husband\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"宅\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "harm, injury", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"害\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "害", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"harm, injury\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ガイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"害\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "distribute, spouse, exile, rationing", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"配\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "配", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"distribute, spouse, exile, rationing\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"配\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くば.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"配\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "admonish, commandment", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"警\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "警", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"admonish, commandment\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"警\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いまし.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"警\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bring up, grow up, raise, rear", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"育\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "育", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bring up, grow up, raise, rear\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "イク ハグク.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"育\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そだ.つ そだ.ち そだ.てる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"育\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "seat, mat, occasion, place", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"席\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "席", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"seat, mat, occasion, place\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セキ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"席\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むしろ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"席\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "call on, visit, look up, offer sympathy", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"訪\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "訪", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"call on, visit, look up, offer sympathy\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ホウ ト.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"訪\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おとず.れる たず.ねる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"訪\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ride, power, multiplication, record, counter for vehicles, board, mount, join", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"乗\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "乗", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ride, power, multiplication, record, counter for vehicles, board, mount, join\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジョウ ショウ ノ.セ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"乗\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "の.る -の.り", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"乗\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "remainder, leftover, balance", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"残\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "残", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"remainder, leftover, balance\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ザン サン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"残\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のこ.る のこ.す そこな.う のこ.り", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"残\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "concept, think, idea, thought", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"想\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "想", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"concept, think, idea, thought\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソウ ソ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"想\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おも.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"想\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "voice", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"声\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "声", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"voice\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セイ ショウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"声\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こえ こわ-", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"声\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "wish, sense, idea, thought, feeling, desire, attention", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"念\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "念", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"wish, sense, idea, thought, feeling, desire, attention\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ネン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"念\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "help, rescue, assist", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"助\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "助", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"help, rescue, assist\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジョ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"助\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たす.ける たす.かる す.ける すけ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"助\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "labor, thank for, reward for, toil, trouble", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"労\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "労", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"labor, thank for, reward for, toil, trouble\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ロウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"労\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ろう.する いたわ.る いた.ずき ねぎら つか.れる ねぎら.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"労\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "example, custom, usage, precedent", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"例\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "例", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"example, custom, usage, precedent\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"例\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たと.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"例\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sort of thing, so, if so, in that case, well", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"然\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "然", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sort of thing, so, if so, in that case, well\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゼン ネン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"然\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しか しか.り しか.し さ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"然\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "limit, restrict, to best of ability", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"限\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "限", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"limit, restrict, to best of ability\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゲン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"限\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かぎ.る かぎ.り -かぎ.り", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"限\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "chase, drive away, follow, pursue, meanwhile", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"追\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "追", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"chase, drive away, follow, pursue, meanwhile\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ツイ オ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"追\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "make a deal, selling, dealing in, merchant", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"商\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "商", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"make a deal, selling, dealing in, merchant\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショウ アキナ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"商\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "leaf, plane, lobe, needle, blade, spear, counter for flat things, fragment, piece", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"葉\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "葉", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"leaf, plane, lobe, needle, blade, spear, counter for flat things, fragment, piece\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヨウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"葉\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "transmit, go along, walk along, follow, report, communicate, legend, tradition", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"伝\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "伝", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"transmit, go along, walk along, follow, report, communicate, legend, tradition\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "デン テン ツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"伝\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つた.わる つた.える つた.う つだ.う -づた.い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"伝\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "work, (kokuji)", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"働\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "働", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"work, (kokuji)\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ドウ リュク リキ ロク リョク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"働\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はたら.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"働\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shape, form, style", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"形\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "形", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shape, form, style\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケイ ギョウ ナ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"形\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かた -がた かたち", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"形\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "scenery, view", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"景\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "景", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"scenery, view\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"景\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fall, drop, come down", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"落\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "落", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fall, drop, come down\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ラク オ.ト", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"落\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お.ちる お.ち", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"落\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fond, pleasing, like something", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"好\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "好", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fond, pleasing, like something\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ イ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"好\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "この.む す.く よ.い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"好\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "retreat, withdraw, retire, resign, repel, expel, reject", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"退\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "退", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"retreat, withdraw, retire, resign, repel, expel, reject\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"退\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しりぞ.く しりぞ.ける ひ.く の.く の.ける ど.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"退\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "head, counter for large animals", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"頭\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "頭", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"head, counter for large animals\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トウ ズ ト カブ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"頭\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あたま かしら -がしら", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"頭\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "defeat, negative, -, minus, bear, owe, assume a responsibility", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"負\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "負", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"defeat, negative, -, minus, bear, owe, assume a responsibility\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"負\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ま.ける ま.かす お.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"負\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "transit, ford, ferry, cross, import, deliver, diameter, migrate", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"渡\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "渡", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"transit, ford, ferry, cross, import, deliver, diameter, migrate\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ト ワタ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"渡\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わた.る -わた.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"渡\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lose, error, fault, disadvantage, loss", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"失\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "失", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lose, error, fault, disadvantage, loss\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"失\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うしな.う う.せる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"失\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "distinction, difference, variation, discrepancy, margin, balance", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"差\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "差", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"distinction, difference, variation, discrepancy, margin, balance\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"差\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さ.す さ.し", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"差\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "end, close, tip, powder, posterity", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"末\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "末", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"end, close, tip, powder, posterity\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "マツ バツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"末\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すえ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"末\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "guard, protect, defend, obey", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"守\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "守", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"guard, protect, defend, obey\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シュ ス カ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"守\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まも.る まも.り もり -もり", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"守\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "young, if, perhaps, possibly, low number, immature", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"若\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "若", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"young, if, perhaps, possibly, low number, immature\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジャク ニャク ニャ モ.シク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"若\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わか.い わか- も.しくわ も.し", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"若\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "species, kind, class, variety, seed", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"種\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "種", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"species, kind, class, variety, seed\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シュ -グ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"種\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たね", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"種\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "beauty, beautiful", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"美\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "美", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"beauty, beautiful\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ビ ミ ウツク.シ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"美\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fate, command, decree, destiny, life, appoint", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"命\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "命", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fate, command, decree, destiny, life, appoint\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "メイ ミョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"命\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いのち", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"命\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "blessing, fortune, luck, wealth", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"福\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "福", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"blessing, fortune, luck, wealth\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"福\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ambition, full moon, hope, desire, aspire to, expect", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"望\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "望", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ambition, full moon, hope, desire, aspire to, expect\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ボウ モウ モ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"望\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のぞ.む", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"望\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "un-, mistake, negative, injustice, non-", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"非\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "非", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"un-, mistake, negative, injustice, non-\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"非\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あら.ず", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"非\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "outlook, look, appearance, condition, view", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"観\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "観", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"outlook, look, appearance, condition, view\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"観\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "み.る しめ.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"観\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "guess, presume, surmise, judge, understand", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"察\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "察", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"guess, presume, surmise, judge, understand\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"察\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grade, steps, stairs", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"段\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "段", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grade, steps, stairs\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ダン タン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"段\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sideways, side, horizontal, width, woof", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"横\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "横", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sideways, side, horizontal, width, woof\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "オウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"横\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よこ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"横\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "deep, heighten, intensify, strengthen", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"深\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "深", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"deep, heighten, intensify, strengthen\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"深\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふか.い -ぶか.い ふか.まる ふか.める み-", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"深\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "have the honor to, sign of the monkey, 3-5PM, ninth sign of Chinese zodiac", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"申\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "申", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"have the honor to, sign of the monkey, 3-5PM, ninth sign of Chinese zodiac\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"申\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もう.す もう.し- さる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"申\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "Esq., way, manner, situation, polite suffix", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"様\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "様", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"Esq., way, manner, situation, polite suffix\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヨウ ショウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"様\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さま さん", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"様\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "property, money, wealth, assets", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"財\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "財", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"property, money, wealth, assets\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ザイ サイ ゾ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"財\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "harbor", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"港\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "港", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"harbor\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"港\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みなと", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"港\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "discriminating, know, write", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"識\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "識", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"discriminating, know, write\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"識\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "call, call out to, invite", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"呼\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "呼", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"call, call out to, invite\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コ ヨ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"呼\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "accomplished, reach, arrive, attain", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"達\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "達", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"accomplished, reach, arrive, attain\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タツ ダ -タ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"達\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "good, pleasing, skilled", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"良\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "良", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"good, pleasing, skilled\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "リョウ -イ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"良\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よ.い -よ.い い.い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"良\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "climate, season, weather", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"候\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "候", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"climate, season, weather\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"候\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そうろう", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"候\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "extent, degree, law, formula, distance, limits, amount", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"程\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "程", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"extent, degree, law, formula, distance, limits, amount\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テイ -ホ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"程\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほど", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"程\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "full, enough, pride, satisfy", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"満\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "満", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"full, enough, pride, satisfy\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "マン バン ミ.タ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"満\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "み.ちる み.つ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"満\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "failure, defeat, reversal", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"敗\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "敗", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"failure, defeat, reversal\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"敗\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やぶ.れる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"敗\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "price, cost, value", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"値\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "値", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"price, cost, value\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "チ アタ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"値\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ね", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"値\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "stab, protruding, thrusting, thrust, pierce, prick", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"突\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "突", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"stab, protruding, thrusting, thrust, pierce, prick\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トツ カ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"突\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つ.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"突\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ray, light", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"光\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "光", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ray, light\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ ヒカ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"光\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひか.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"光\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "path, route, road, distance", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"路\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "路", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"path, route, road, distance\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ロ ル", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"路\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "-じ みち", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"路\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "department, course, section", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"科\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "科", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"department, course, section\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "volume, product (x*y), acreage, contents, pile up, stack, load, amass", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"積\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "積", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"volume, product (x*y), acreage, contents, pile up, stack, load, amass\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セキ ツ.モ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"積\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つ.む -づ.み つ.もる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"積\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "other, another, the others", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"他\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "他", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"other, another, the others\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"他\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほか", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"他\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dispose, manage, deal with, sentence, condemn, act, behave, place", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"処\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "処", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dispose, manage, deal with, sentence, condemn, act, behave, place\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"処\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ところ -こ お.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"処\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "plump, thick, big around", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"太\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "太", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"plump, thick, big around\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タイ タ フト.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"太\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふと.い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"太\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "guest, visitor, customer, client", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"客\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "客", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"guest, visitor, customer, client\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キャク カク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"客\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "negate, no, noes, refuse, decline, deny", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"否\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "否", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"negate, no, noes, refuse, decline, deny\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"否\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いな いや", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"否\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "expert, teacher, master, army, war", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"師\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "師", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"expert, teacher, master, army, war\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ascend, climb up", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"登\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "登", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ascend, climb up\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トウ ト ドウ ショウ チョウ ア.ガ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"登\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のぼ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"登\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "easy, ready to, simple, fortune-telling, divination", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"易\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "易", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"easy, ready to, simple, fortune-telling, divination\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "エキ イ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"易\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やさ.しい やす.い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"易\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "quick, fast", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"速\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "速", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"quick, fast\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソク スミ.ヤ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"速\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はや.い はや- はや.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"速\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "suppose, be aware of, believe, feel", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"存\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "存", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"suppose, be aware of, believe, feel\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソン ゾ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"存\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fly, skip (pages), scatter", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"飛\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "飛", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fly, skip (pages), scatter\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒ -ト.バ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"飛\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "と.ぶ と.ばす", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"飛\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "kill, murder, butcher, slice off, split, diminish, reduce, spoil", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"殺\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "殺", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"kill, murder, butcher, slice off, split, diminish, reduce, spoil\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サツ サイ セツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"殺\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ころ.す -ごろ.し そ.ぐ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"殺\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "nickname, number, item, title, pseudonym, name, call", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"号\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "号", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"nickname, number, item, title, pseudonym, name, call\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゴウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"号\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さけ.ぶ よびな", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"号\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "simple, one, single, merely", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"単\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "単", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"simple, one, single, merely\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"単\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひとえ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"単\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "squat, seat, cushion, gathering, sit", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"座\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "座", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"squat, seat, cushion, gathering, sit\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ザ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"座\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "すわ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"座\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rend, rip, tear, break, destroy, defeat, frustrate", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"破\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "破", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rend, rip, tear, break, destroy, defeat, frustrate\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハ ヤブ.レ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"破\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やぶ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"破\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "exclude, division (x, 3), remove, abolish, cancel, except", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"除\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "除", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"exclude, division (x, 3), remove, abolish, cancel, except\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジョ ジ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"除\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "のぞ.く -よ.け", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"除\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "perfect, completion, end", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"完\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "完", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"perfect, completion, end\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"完\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "descend, precipitate, fall, surrender", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"降\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "降", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"descend, precipitate, fall, surrender\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ ゴ クダ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"降\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お.りる お.ろす ふ.る ふ.り くだ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"降\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "blame, condemn, censure", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"責\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "責", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"blame, condemn, censure\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セキ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"責\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せ.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"責\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "catch, capture", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"捕\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "捕", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"catch, capture\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ホ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"捕\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "と.らえる と.らわれる と.る とら.える とら.われる つか.まえる つか.まる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"捕\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dangerous, fear, uneasy", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"危\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "危", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dangerous, fear, uneasy\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"危\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あぶ.ない あや.うい あや.ぶむ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"危\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "salary, wage, gift, allow, grant, bestow on", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"給\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "給", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"salary, wage, gift, allow, grant, bestow on\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キュウ -タマ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"給\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たま.う たも.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"給\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "suffering, trial, worry, hardship, feel bitter, scowl", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"苦\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "苦", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"suffering, trial, worry, hardship, feel bitter, scowl\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"苦\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くる.しい -ぐる.しい くる.しむ くる.しめる にが.い にが.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"苦\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "welcome, meet, greet", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"迎\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "迎", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"welcome, meet, greet\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゲイ ムカ.エ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"迎\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "park, garden, yard, farm", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"園\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "園", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"park, garden, yard, farm\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "エン ソ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"園\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tool, utensil, means, possess, ingredients, counter for armor, suits, sets of furniture", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"具\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "具", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tool, utensil, means, possess, ingredients, counter for armor, suits, sets of furniture\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "グ ツブサ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"具\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "そな.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"具\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "resign, word, term, expression", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"辞\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "辞", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"resign, word, term, expression\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"辞\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "や.める いな.む", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"辞\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cause, factor, be associated with, depend on, be limited to", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"因\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "因", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cause, factor, be associated with, depend on, be limited to\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "イン チナ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"因\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"因\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "horse", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"馬\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "馬", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"horse\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "バ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"馬\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "うま うま-", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"馬\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "love, affection, favourite", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"愛\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "愛", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"love, affection, favourite\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アイ イト.シ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"愛\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "wealth, enrich, abundant", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"富\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "富", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"wealth, enrich, abundant\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フ フウ ト", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"富\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "と.む", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"富\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "he, that, the", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"彼\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "彼", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"he, that, the\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒ カ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"彼\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かれ かの", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"彼\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "un-, not yet, hitherto, still, even now, sign of the ram, 1-3PM, eighth sign of Chinese zodiac", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"未\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "未", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"un-, not yet, hitherto, still, even now, sign of the ram, 1-3PM, eighth sign of Chinese zodiac\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ミ ビ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"未\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いま.だ ま.だ ひつじ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"未\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dance, flit, circle, wheel", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"舞\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "舞", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dance, flit, circle, wheel\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ブ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"舞\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ま.う -ま.う まい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"舞\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "deceased, the late, dying, perish", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"亡\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "亡", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"deceased, the late, dying, perish\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ボウ モウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"亡\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "な.い な.き- ほろ.びる ほろ.ぶ ほろ.ぼす", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"亡\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cool, cold (beer, person), chill", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"冷\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "冷", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cool, cold (beer, person), chill\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"冷\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つめ.たい ひ.える ひ.や ひ.ややか ひ.やす ひ.やかす さ.める さ.ます", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"冷\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "suitable, occasional, rare, qualified, capable", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"適\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "適", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"suitable, occasional, rare, qualified, capable\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テキ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"適\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かな.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"適\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lady, woman, wife, bride", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"婦\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "婦", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lady, woman, wife, bride\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "draw near, stop in, bring near, gather, collect, send, forward", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"寄\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "寄", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"draw near, stop in, bring near, gather, collect, send, forward\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キ ヨ.セ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"寄\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よ.る -よ.り", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"寄\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "crowded, mixture, in bulk, included, (kokuji)", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"込\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "込", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"crowded, mixture, in bulk, included, (kokuji)\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コ.メ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"込\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "-こ.む こ.む こ.み -こ.み", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"込\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "face, expression", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"顔\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "顔", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"face, expression\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ガン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"顔\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かお", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"顔\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sort, kind, variety, class, genus", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"類\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "類", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sort, kind, variety, class, genus\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ルイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"類\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たぐ.い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"類\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "too much, myself, surplus, other, remainder", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"余\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "余", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"too much, myself, surplus, other, remainder\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヨ アマ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"余\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あま.る あま.り", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"余\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "king, rule, magnate", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"王\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "王", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"king, rule, magnate\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "オウ -ノ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"王\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "return, answer, fade, repay", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"返\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "返", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"return, answer, fade, repay\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヘン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"返\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かえ.す -かえ.す かえ.る -かえ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"返\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "wife, spouse", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"妻\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "妻", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"wife, spouse\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サイ ツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"妻\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "stature, height, back, behind, disobey, defy, go back on, rebel", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"背\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "背", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"stature, height, back, behind, disobey, defy, go back on, rebel\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"背\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "せ せい そむ.く そむ.ける", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"背\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "heat, temperature, fever, mania, passion", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"熱\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "熱", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"heat, temperature, fever, mania, passion\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ネツ アツ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"熱\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "inn, lodging, relay station, dwell, lodge, be pregnant, home, dwelling", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"宿\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "宿", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"inn, lodging, relay station, dwell, lodge, be pregnant, home, dwelling\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シュク ヤド.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"宿\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "やど やど.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"宿\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "medicine, chemical, enamel, gunpowder, benefit", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"薬\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "薬", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"medicine, chemical, enamel, gunpowder, benefit\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヤク クス", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"薬\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "precipitous, inaccessible place, impregnable position, steep place, sharp eyes", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"険\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "険", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"precipitous, inaccessible place, impregnable position, steep place, sharp eyes\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ケン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"険\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けわ.しい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"険\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "trust, request", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"頼\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "頼", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"trust, request\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ライ タヨ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"頼\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たの.む たの.もしい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"頼\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "memorize, learn, remember, awake, sober up", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"覚\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "覚", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"memorize, learn, remember, awake, sober up\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"覚\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おぼ.える さ.ます さ.める さと.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"覚\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ship, boat", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"船\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "船", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ship, boat\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"船\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ふね ふな", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"船\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "route, way, road", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"途\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "途", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"route, way, road\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "permit, approve", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"許\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "許", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"permit, approve\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キョ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"許\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆる.す もと", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"許\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "slip out, extract, pull out, pilfer, quote, remove, omit", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"抜\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "抜", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"slip out, extract, pull out, pilfer, quote, remove, omit\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "バツ ハツ ハイ ヌ.カ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"抜\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぬ.く -ぬ.く ぬ.き ぬ.ける ぬ.かす", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"抜\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "convenience", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"便\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "便", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"convenience\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ベン ビン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"便\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たよ.り", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"便\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "detain, fasten, halt, stop", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"留\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "留", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"detain, fasten, halt, stop\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "リュウ ル ルウブ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"留\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "と.める と.まる とど.める とど.まる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"留\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "guilt, sin, crime, fault, blame, offense", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"罪\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "罪", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"guilt, sin, crime, fault, blame, offense\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ザイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"罪\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つみ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"罪\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "toil, diligent, as much as possible", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"努\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "努", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"toil, diligent, as much as possible\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ド", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"努\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つと.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"努\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "refined, ghost, fairy, energy, vitality, semen, excellence, purity, skill", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"精\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "精", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"refined, ghost, fairy, energy, vitality, semen, excellence, purity, skill\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セイ ショウ シヤ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"精\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "scatter, disperse, spend, squander", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"散\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "散", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"scatter, disperse, spend, squander\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サン バ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"散\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ち.る ち.らす -ち.らす ち.らかす ち.らかる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"散\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "quiet", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"静\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "静", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"quiet\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セイ ジョウ シズ.メ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"静\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "しず- しず.か しず.まる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"静\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "marriage", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"婚\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "婚", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"marriage\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"婚\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "rejoice, take pleasure in", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"喜\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "喜", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"rejoice, take pleasure in\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キ ヨロコ.バ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"喜\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よろこ.ぶ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"喜\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "floating, float, rise to surface", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"浮\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "浮", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"floating, float, rise to surface\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フ ウ.カベ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"浮\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "う.く う.かれる う.かぶ む", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"浮\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "discontinue, beyond, sever, cut off, abstain, interrupt, suppress", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"絶\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "絶", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"discontinue, beyond, sever, cut off, abstain, interrupt, suppress\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゼツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"絶\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "た.える た.やす た.つ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"絶\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "happiness, blessing, fortune", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"幸\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "幸", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"happiness, blessing, fortune\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ シアワ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"幸\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さいわ.い さち", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"幸\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "push, stop, check, subdue, attach, seize, weight, shove, press, seal, do in spite of", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"押\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "押", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"push, stop, check, subdue, attach, seize, weight, shove, press, seal, do in spite of\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "オウ オサ.エ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"押\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お.す お.し- お.っ- お.さえる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"押\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "overthrow, fall, collapse, drop, break down", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"倒\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "倒", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"overthrow, fall, collapse, drop, break down\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"倒\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たお.れる -だお.れ たお.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"倒\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "etc., and so forth, class (first), quality, equal, similar", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"等\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "等", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"etc., and so forth, class (first), quality, equal, similar\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トウ -", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"等\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ひと.しい など", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"等\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "old man, old age, grow old", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"老\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "老", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"old man, old age, grow old\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ロウ フ.ケ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"老\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お.いる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"老\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bend, music, melody, composition, pleasure, injustice, fault, curve, crooked, perverse, lean", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"曲\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "曲", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bend, music, melody, composition, pleasure, injustice, fault, curve, crooked, perverse, lean\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キョク マ.ゲ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"曲\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ま.がる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"曲\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pay, clear out, prune, banish, dispose of", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"払\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "払", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pay, clear out, prune, banish, dispose of\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フツ ヒツ ホツ -バラ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"払\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はら.う -はら.い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"払\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "courtyard, garden, yard", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"庭\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "庭", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"courtyard, garden, yard\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "テイ ニ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"庭\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "junior, emptiness, vanity, futility, uselessness, ephemeral thing, gang, set, party, people", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"徒\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "徒", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"junior, emptiness, vanity, futility, uselessness, ephemeral thing, gang, set, party, people\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ト ア", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"徒\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いたずら", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"徒\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "diligence, become employed, serve", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"勤\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "勤", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"diligence, become employed, serve\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キン ゴン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"勤\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つと.める -づと.め つと.まる いそ.しむ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"勤\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "slow, late, back, later", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"遅\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遅", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"slow, late, back, later\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "チ オソ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"遅\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おく.れる おく.らす", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"遅\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "reside, to be, exist, live with", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"居\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "居", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"reside, to be, exist, live with\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キョ コ オ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"居\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "い.る -い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"居\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "miscellaneous", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"雑\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "雑", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"miscellaneous\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ザツ ゾウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"雑\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まじ.える まじ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"雑\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "beckon, invite, summon, engage", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"招\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "招", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"beckon, invite, summon, engage\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"招\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まね.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"招\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "quandary, become distressed, annoyed", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"困\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "困", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"quandary, become distressed, annoyed\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"困\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こま.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"困\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lack, gap, fail", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"欠\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "欠", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lack, gap, fail\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あくび", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"欠\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grow late, night watch, sit up late, of course", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"更\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "更", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grow late, night watch, sit up late, of course\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"更\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さら さら.に ふ.ける ふ.かす", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"更\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "engrave, cut fine, chop, hash, mince, time, carving", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"刻\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "刻", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"engrave, cut fine, chop, hash, mince, time, carving\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "コク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"刻\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きざ.む きざ.み", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"刻\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "approve, praise, title or inscription on picture, assist, agree with", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"賛\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "賛", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"approve, praise, title or inscription on picture, assist, agree with\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"賛\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たす.ける たた.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"賛\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "embrace, hug, hold in arms", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"抱\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "抱", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"embrace, hug, hold in arms\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ホウ カカ.エ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"抱\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "だ.く いだ.く", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"抱\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "crime, sin, offense", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"犯\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "犯", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"crime, sin, offense\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハン ボン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"犯\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おか.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"犯\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fear, dread, awe", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"恐\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "恐", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fear, dread, awe\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"恐\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おそ.れる おそ.る おそ.ろしい こわ.い こわ.がる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"恐\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "breath, respiration, son, interest (on money)", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"息\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "息", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"breath, respiration, son, interest (on money)\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"息\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いき", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"息\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "distant, far", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"遠\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遠", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"distant, far\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "エン オン トオ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"遠\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "re-, return, revert, resume, restore, go backwards", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"戻\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "戻", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"re-, return, revert, resume, restore, go backwards\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"戻\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "もど.す もど.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"戻\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "petition, request, vow, wish, hope", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"願\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "願", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"petition, request, vow, wish, hope\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ガン -ネガ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"願\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねが.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"願\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "picture, drawing, painting, sketch", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"絵\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "絵", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"picture, drawing, painting, sketch\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カイ エ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"絵\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "surpass, cross over, move to, exceed, Vietnam", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"越\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "越", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"surpass, cross over, move to, exceed, Vietnam\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "エツ オツ -ゴ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"越\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こ.す -こ.す -ご.し こ.える", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"越\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "longing, covetousness, greed, passion, desire, craving", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"欲\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "欲", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"longing, covetousness, greed, passion, desire, craving\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヨク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"欲\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ほっ.する ほ.しい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"欲\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "pain, hurt, damage, bruise", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"痛\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "痛", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"pain, hurt, damage, bruise\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ツウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"痛\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いた.い いた.む いた.ましい いた.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"痛\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "laugh", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"笑\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "笑", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"laugh\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショウ エ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"笑\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わら.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"笑\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mutually, reciprocally, together", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"互\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "互", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mutually, reciprocally, together\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゴ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"互\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たが.い かたみ.に", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"互\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "bundle, sheaf, ream, tie in bundles, govern, manage, control", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"束\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "束", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"bundle, sheaf, ream, tie in bundles, govern, manage, control\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"束\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たば たば.ねる つか つか.ねる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"束\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "becoming, resemble, counterfeit, imitate, suitable", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"似\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "似", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"becoming, resemble, counterfeit, imitate, suitable\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジ ヒ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"似\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "に.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"似\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "file, row, rank, tier, column", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"列\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "列", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"file, row, rank, tier, column\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レツ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"列\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grope, search, look for", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"探\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "探", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grope, search, look for\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "タン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"探\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さぐ.る さが.す", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"探\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "escape, flee, shirk, evade, set free", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"逃\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "逃", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"escape, flee, shirk, evade, set free\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"逃\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "に.げる に.がす のが.す のが.れる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"逃\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "play", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"遊\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "遊", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"play\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ユウ ユ アソ.バ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"遊\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あそ.ぶ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"遊\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "astray, be perplexed, in doubt, lost, err, illusion", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"迷\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "迷", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"astray, be perplexed, in doubt, lost, err, illusion\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "メイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"迷\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まよ.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"迷\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dream, vision, illusion", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"夢\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "夢", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dream, vision, illusion\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ム ボウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"夢\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゆめ ゆめ.みる くら.い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"夢\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "old boy, name-suffix", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"君\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "君", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"old boy, name-suffix\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "クン -ギ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"君\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "きみ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"君\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "closed, shut", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"閉\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "閉", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"closed, shut\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヘイ タ.テ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"閉\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "と.じる と.ざす し.める し.まる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"閉\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "thong, beginning, inception, end, cord, strap", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"緒\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "緒", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"thong, beginning, inception, end, cord, strap\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ショ チョ イトグ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"緒\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"緒\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "fold, break, fracture, bend, yield, submit", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"折\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "折", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"fold, break, fracture, bend, yield, submit\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セツ オ.レ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"折\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "お.る おり お.り -お.り", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"折\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "grass, weeds, herbs, pasture, write, draft", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"草\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "草", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"grass, weeds, herbs, pasture, write, draft\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソウ -グ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"草\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くさ くさ-", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"草\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "livelihood, make a living, spend time", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"暮\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "暮", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"livelihood, make a living, spend time\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ボ ク.ラ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"暮\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "く.れる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"暮\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sake, alcohol", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"酒\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "酒", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sake, alcohol\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シュ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"酒\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さけ さか", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"酒\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "jail cell, grieve, sad, deplore, regret", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"悲\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "悲", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"jail cell, grieve, sad, deplore, regret\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"悲\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "かな.しい かな.しむ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"悲\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "clear up", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"晴\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "晴", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"clear up\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セイ ハ.ラ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"晴\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "は.れる は.れ は.れ- -ば.れ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"晴\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hang, suspend, depend, arrive at, tax, pour", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"掛\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "掛", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hang, suspend, depend, arrive at, tax, pour\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カイ ケイ -ガカ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"掛\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "か.ける -か.ける か.け -か.け -が.け か.かる -か.かる -が.かる か.かり -が.かり かかり", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"掛\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "arrival, proceed, reach, attain, result in", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"到\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "到", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"arrival, proceed, reach, attain, result in\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"到\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いた.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"到\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "lie down, sleep, rest, bed, remain unsold", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"寝\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "寝", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"lie down, sleep, rest, bed, remain unsold\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"寝\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ね.る ね.かす い.ぬ みたまや や.める", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"寝\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "darkness, disappear, shade, informal, grow dark, be blinded", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"暗\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "暗", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"darkness, disappear, shade, informal, grow dark, be blinded\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "アン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"暗\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くら.い", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"暗\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "steal, rob, pilfer", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"盗\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "盗", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"steal, rob, pilfer\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "トウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"盗\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ぬす.む ぬす.み", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"盗\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "suck, imbibe, inhale, sip", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"吸\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "吸", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"suck, imbibe, inhale, sip\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キュウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"吸\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "す.う", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"吸\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sunshine, yang principle, positive, male, heaven, daytime", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"陽\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "陽", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sunshine, yang principle, positive, male, heaven, daytime\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヨウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"陽\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "honorable, manipulate, govern", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"御\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "御", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"honorable, manipulate, govern\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ギョ ゴ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"御\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "おん- お- み", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"御\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "tooth, cog", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"歯\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "歯", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"tooth, cog\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "シ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"歯\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "よわい は よわ.い よわい.する", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"歯\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "forget", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"忘\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "忘", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"forget\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ボウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"忘\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "わす.れる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"忘\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "snow", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"雪\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "雪", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"snow\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セツ ユ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"雪\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "blow, breathe, puff, emit, smoke", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"吹\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "吹", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"blow, breathe, puff, emit, smoke\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "スイ フ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"吹\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "daughter, girl", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"娘\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "娘", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"daughter, girl\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"娘\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むすめ こ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"娘\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "mistake, err, do wrong, mislead", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"誤\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "誤", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"mistake, err, do wrong, mislead\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ゴ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"誤\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "あやま.る -あやま.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"誤\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "wash, inquire into, probe", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"洗\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "洗", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"wash, inquire into, probe\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セン アラ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"洗\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "accustomed, get used to, become experienced", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"慣\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "慣", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"accustomed, get used to, become experienced\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"慣\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "な.れる な.らす", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"慣\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "salute, bow, ceremony, thanks, remuneration", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"礼\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "礼", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"salute, bow, ceremony, thanks, remuneration\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "レイ ラ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"礼\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "window, pane", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"窓\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "窓", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"window, pane\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソウ ス", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"窓\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まど てんまど けむだし", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"窓\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "once upon a time, antiquity, old times", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"昔\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "昔", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"once upon a time, antiquity, old times\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "セキ シャク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"昔\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "むかし", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"昔\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "poverty, poor", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"貧\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "貧", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"poverty, poor\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒン ビン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"貧\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "まず.しい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"貧\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "angry, be offended", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"怒\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "怒", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"angry, be offended\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ド ヌ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"怒\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いか.る おこ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"怒\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "swim", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"泳\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "泳", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"swim\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "エイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"泳\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "およ.ぐ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"泳\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ancestor, pioneer, founder", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"祖\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "祖", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ancestor, pioneer, founder\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "counter for cupfuls, wine glass, glass, toast", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"杯\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "杯", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"counter for cupfuls, wine glass, glass, toast\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"杯\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "さかずき", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"杯\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "exhausted, tire, weary", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"疲\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "疲", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"exhausted, tire, weary\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ヒ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"疲\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "つか.れる -づか.れ つか.らす", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"疲\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "all, everything", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"皆\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "皆", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"all, everything\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カイ ミン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"皆\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "みな", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"皆\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "chirp, cry, bark, sound, ring, echo, honk", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"鳴\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "鳴", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"chirp, cry, bark, sound, ring, echo, honk\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "メイ ナ.ラ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"鳴\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "な.く な.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"鳴\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "abdomen, belly, stomach", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"腹\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "腹", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"abdomen, belly, stomach\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フク", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"腹\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はら", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"腹\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "smoke", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"煙\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "煙", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"smoke\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "エン ケム.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"煙\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "けむ.る けむり", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"煙\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "sleep, die, sleepy", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"眠\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "眠", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"sleep, die, sleepy\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ミン ネム.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"眠\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねむ.る", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"眠\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "dreadful, be frightened, fearful", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"怖\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "怖", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"dreadful, be frightened, fearful\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "フ ホ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"怖\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "こわ.い こわ.がる お.じる おそ.れる", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"怖\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ear", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"耳\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "耳", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"ear\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ジ ミ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"耳\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "place on the head, receive, top of head, top, summit, peak", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"頂\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "頂", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"place on the head, receive, top of head, top, summit, peak\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "チョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"頂\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いただ.く いただき", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"頂\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "box, chest, case, bin, railway car", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"箱\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "箱", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"box, chest, case, bin, railway car\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ソウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"箱\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "はこ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"箱\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "nightfall, night", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"晩\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "晩", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"nightfall, night\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "バン", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"晩\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cold", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"寒\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "寒", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cold\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カン サム.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"寒\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "hair of the head", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"髪\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "髪", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"hair of the head\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ハツ カ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"髪\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "busy, occupied, restless", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"忙\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "忙", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"busy, occupied, restless\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ボウ モウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"忙\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いそが.しい せわ.しい おそ.れる うれえるさま", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"忙\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "genius, years old, cubic shaku", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"才\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "才", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"genius, years old, cubic shaku\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "サイ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"才\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shoes", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"靴\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "靴", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shoes\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "カ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"靴\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "くつ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"靴\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "shame, dishonor", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"恥\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "恥", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"shame, dishonor\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "チ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"恥\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "は.じる はじ は.じらう は.ずかしい", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"恥\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "accidentally, even number, couple, man & wife, same kind", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"偶\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "偶", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"accidentally, even number, couple, man & wife, same kind\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "グウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"偶\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "たま", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"偶\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "admirable, greatness, remarkable, conceited, famous, excellent", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"偉\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "偉", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"admirable, greatness, remarkable, conceited, famous, excellent\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "イ エラ.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"偉\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "cat", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"猫\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "猫", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"cat\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ビョウ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"猫\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "ねこ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"猫\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "how many, how much, how far, how long", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"幾\" what is the definition?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "幾", 
            "question": "Given the definition \"how many, how much, how far, how long\" what is the kanji?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "キ イク.", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"幾\" what is the On reading(s)?"
        }, 
        {
            "answer": "いく- いく.つ", 
            "question": "Given the kanji \"幾\" what is the Kun reading(s)?"
        }
    ]
}